Guide to the News Service Biographical Files, circa 1930s - 2004 UA.27.01.0003
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Simpkins, Thomas (Box 141)
- Simpson, Dorothy (Box 141)
- Simpson, Dorothy Lewis, Trustee 1988- (Box 118)
- Simpson, Ida (Box 141)
- Simpson, Ida Harper (Box 100)
- Simpson, James R. (Box 155)
- Simpson, James Robert (Box 51)
- Simpson, Ormond (Box 100)
- Simpson, Ormond (Box 141)
- Simpson, Robert T. (Box 100)
- Simpson, Robert T. (Box 141)
- Simpson, William Hays (Box 51)
- Simpson, William Hays (Box 141)
- Sindler, Allan P. (Box 100)
- Sindler, Allan P. (Box 155)
- Sindler, Allan P. (Box 141)
- Singer, David L. (Box 100)
- Singer, Kay (Box 100)
- Sinoit, Nasser (Box 51)
- Sitkin, Sim (Box 100)
- Skarulis, Patricia (Box 100)
- Skarulis, Patricia (Box 141)
- Sketch, Michael H. (Box 100)
- Skinner, Celettes (Box 100)
- Skinner, Leroy C. (Box 100)
- Skolaut, Milton (Box 100)
- Sladen, Robert Neil (Box 100)
- Slaughter, Frank G. (Box 113)
  Biographical information. Alumnus; M.D.; Author
- Slavik, Bohdan (Box 100)
- Slay, James M. (Box 100)
- Slay, James M. (Box 141)
- Slay, James Matthew (Box 51)
- Slente, Cris (Box 100)
- Slinn, Ronald John (Box 100)
- Slinn, Ronald John (Box 141)
- Sloan, Frank (Box 100)
- Sloan, Steve (Box 51)
- Sloate, Steve (Box 100)
- Slotkin, Theodore A. (Box 100)
- Smeal, Eleanor (Box 113)
  Biographical information. Alumna
- Smith, Grover C., Jr. (Box 100)
- Smith, Harmon (Box 141)
- Smith, (Mrs. Hazen) Ruth Slack (Box 52)
- Smith, Albert (Box 100)
- Smith, Albert (Box 155)
- Smith, Arline (Box 100)
- Smith, Arline (Box 141)
- Smith, Barbara Herrnstein (Box 100)
- Smith, Barbara Herrnstein (Box 141)
- Smith, Brian Cantwell (Box 100)
- Smith, Brian Cantwell, 2001 (Box 100)
- Smith, Cabell (Box 100)
- Smith, Carl W., Jr. (Box 100)
- Smith, Carl W., Jr. (Box 141)
- Smith, Carl William, Jr. (Box 155)
- Smith, Carol A. (Box 100)
- Smith, Charles M., Trustee to 2001, Trustee (Box 118)
- Smith, Charlie Mike (Box 100)
- Smith, Charlie Mike (Box 155)
- Smith, Clayton A. (Box 100)
- Smith, Connie U. (Box 51)
- Smith, David Alexander (Box 100)
- Smith, David Alexander (Box 141)
- Smith, David T., 2 folders (Box 52)
- Smith, David T. (Box 100)
- Smith, David T. (Box 155)
- Smith, David T. (Box 141)
- Smith, Deborah (Box 100)
- Smith, Diana (Box 100)
- Smith, Diana (Box 141)
- Smith, Don (Box 100)
- Smith, Don (Box 141)
- Smith, Don (Box 155)
- Smith, Dwight Moody, Jr. (Box 100)
- Smith, Dwight Moody, Jr. (Box 141)
- Smith, Dwight Noody Jr. (Box 155)
- Smith, Edward F. (Box 100)
- Smith, Grover C., Jr. (Box 155)
- Smith, Grover C., Jr. (Box 141)
- Smith, H. Shelton (Box 52)
- Smith, H. Shelton (Box 101)
- Smith, Harmon (Box 101)
- Smith, Harmon (Box 155)
- Smith, Hazen (Box 101)
- Smith, Hazen (Box 141)
- Smith, Herbert (Box 141)
- Smith, Herbert, Trustee (Box 118)
- Smith, Hilary (Box 101)
- Smith, Hilrie Shelton (Box 141)
- Smith, J. Benjamin (Box 52)
- Smith, J. Benjamin (Box 141)
- Smith, J. Graham (Box 52)
- Smith, J. Graham (Box 101)
- Smith, J. Graham (Box 141)
- Smith, J. Graham (Box 155)
- Smith, J. Lawton (Box 101)
- Smith, J. R. (Box 101)
- Smith, James E. (Box 101)
- Smith, James Raymond (Box 141)
- Smith, James Raymond, d. 2/1987, Trustee (Box 118)
- Smith, Joel (Box 101)
- Smith, Joel (Box 141)
- Smith, Kathleen K. (Box 101)
- Smith, L. W., Jr. (Box 101)
- Smith, Lanty (Box 141)
- Smith, Lanty, Trustee (Box 118)
- Smith, Leroy Paschal (Box 52)
- Smith, Leroy Paschal (Box 141)
- Smith, Peter (Box 101)
- Smith, Peter (Box 141)
- Smith, Peter (Box 155)
- Smith, Ralph (Box 52)
- Smith, Richard S. (Box 101)
- Smith, Richard S. (Box 155)
- Smith, Richard S. (Box 141)
- Smith, Robert (Box 141)
- Smith, Robert Edward (Box 101)
- Smith, Robert Edward (Box 141)
- Smith, Robert Edward (Box 155)
- Smith, Robert Sydney (Box 52)
- Smith, S. Douglas (Box 101)
- Smith, S. Douglas (Box 141)
- Smith, S. Douglas (Box 155)
- Smith, Stanley (Box 101)
- Smith, Stanley (Box 141)
- Smith, Stephen W. (Box 101)
- Smith, Steven Rathgelo (Box 101)
- Smith, Susan Carlton (Box 52)
- Smith, Susan Carlton (Box 101)
- Smith, Susan Carlton (Box 141)
- Smith, Susan G. (Box 101)
- Smith, Susan G. (Box 141)
- Smith, Susan Gower (Box 52)
- Smith, Tom (Box 101)
- Smith, V. Kerry (Box 101)
- Smith, William C. (Box 101)
- Smith, William C. (Box 141)
- Smith, William M. (Box 101)
- Smith, William V. (Box 101)
- Smith, William V. (Box 155)
- Smith, William V. (Box 141)
- Smith, Willis (Box 141)
- Smith, Willis, Trustee (Box 118)
- Smith, Wirt W. (Box 101)
- Smith, Wirt W. (Box 141)
- Smullin, Frank M. (Box 101)
- Smullin, Frank M. (Box 141)
- Snedeker, Jeffrey (Box 101)
- Sneed, Joseph (Box 101)
- Sneed, Joseph (Box 141)
- Sneed, Joseph (Box 155)
- Snethen, Howard (Box 101)
- Snethen, Howard (Box 141)
- Snethen, Howard (Box 155)
- Snook, Laura (Box 101)
- Snow, William Brewster (Box 101)
- Snow, William Brewster (Box 141)
- Snow, William Brewster (Box 155)
- Snyder, Mike (Box 101)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Naval ROTC, 2001
- Snyderman, Ralph (Box 141)
- Snyderman, Ralph (Box 101)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Health Affairs, Duke Health System
- Sobel, A. I. (Box 156)
- Socolar, Joshua (Box 101)
- Soenksen, Gorden D. (Box 101)
- Soenksen, Gorden D. (Box 141)
- Solterer, Helen (Box 101)
- Somjen, George (Box 101)
- Somjen, George (Box 141)
- Sommer, Joachim R. (Box 101)
- Sommer, Joachim R. (Box 141)
- Sommer, Sally R. (Box 101)
- Soper, Edmund Davison (Box 52)
- Soroush, Ali (Box 52)
- Soroush, Ali (Box 141)
- Sorrentino, Robert (Box 101)
- Sosnik, Doug (Box 113)
  Biographical information. Alumnus; Sr. Advisor to President Bill Clinton
- Southern, J. Albert (Box 101)
- Southgate, Thomas F., Jr. (Box 141)
- Southgate, Thomas F., Jr., Trustee (Box 118)
- Spach, Madison (Box 101)
- Spach, Madison (Box 141)
- Spangler, Dorothy (Box 101)
- Spangler, Dorothy (Box 141)
- Spangler, Dot (Box 156)
- Spangler, Joseph (Box 141)
- Spangler, Joseph (Box 156)
- Sparks, Bertel M. (Box 52)
- Sparks, Bertel M. (Box 141)
- Sparks, Thad (Box 101)
- Spaulding, Jean (Box 101)
- Spaulding, Robert L. (Box 52)
- Spaulding, Robert L. (Box 101)
- Spaulding, Robert L. (Box 156)
- Spaulding, Robert L. (Box 141)
- Speaks, Cooper Phillips (Box 101)
- Spears, Marshall T. (Box 52)
- Spears, Mrs. Marshall T. (Box 141)
- Spears, Mrs. Marshall T., Trustee (Box 118)
- Spector, Marshall (Box 101)
- Speed, Joseph A. (Box 52)
- Speer, Kevin (Box 101)
- Speer, Marcy C. (Box 101)
- Spence, Bessie W. (Box 52)
- Spence, Bessie W. (Box 141)
- Spence, Hersey Everett, 2 folders (Box 52)
- Spence, Hersey Everett (Box 141)
- Spencer, John R. (Box 101)
- Spencer, John R. (Box 156)
- Spencer, John R. (Box 141)
- Spencer, Jon Michael (Box 101)
- Spencer, Jon Michael (Box 141)
- Spangler, Joseph (Box 101)
- Spengler, Joseph John (Box 52)
- Spengler, Joseph John (Box 141)
- Spengler, Joseph John (Box 156)
- Spenner, Kenneth I (Box 102)
- Spicer, Leonard D. (Box 102)
- Spielberger, Charles D. (Box 102)
- Spielberger, Charles D. (Box 141)
- Spiller, Lillian P. (Box 53)
- Spock, Alexander (Box 102)
- Sponer, Hertha (Box 53)
- Sponer, Hertha (Box 141)
- Spong, (Rev.) William (Box 156)
- Spong, William C. (Box 102)
- Spong, William C. (Box 141)
- Spradlin, Wilford W. (Box 53)
- Spragens, Thomas A. (Box 102)
- Springer, John Young (Box 141)
- Springer, John Young (Box 156)
- Springer, Roxanne (Box 102)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Physics, 1998
- Spruill, Carol (Box 102)
- Spurrier, Steve (Box 102)
- Srivastav, Ram Prasad (Box 156)
- Srivastav, Ramprased (Box 102)
- St. Claire, Charles (Box 98)
- St. John, Ancel (Box 98)
- Stack, Carol (Box 102)
- Stack, Richard Sean (Box 102)
- Staddon, John (Box 102)
- Staddon, John (Box 141)
- Staelin, Richard (Box 102)
- Stafford-Smith, Mark (Box 102)
- Stainback, Edward (Box 141)
- Stainback, Edward (Box 156)
- Stairs, Gerald Ray (Box 141)
- Stallard, Eric (Box 102)
- Stambaugh, William (Box 102)
- Stambaugh, William (Box 142)
- Stamler, Jonathon (Box 102)
- Stanbury, Walter Albert, Trustee (Box 118)
- Standbury, Walter Albert (Box 142)
- Stanford, Daniel E. (Box 142)
- Stanford, Donald E. (Box 102)
- Stanford, Donald E. (Box 156)
- Stangle, Dalene (Box 102)
- Stanley, (Lt. Col.) James Lester (Box 142)
- Stanley, (Lt. Col.) James Lester (Box 156)
- Stanley, Dennis K. (Box 102)
- Stanley, Dennis K. (Box 142)
- Stanley, Gordon E. (Box 102)
- Stannett, Vivian T. (Box 102)
- Stansbury, Dale F. (Box 142)
- Starmer, Charles F. (Box 102)
- Starn, Orin (Box 102)
- Starnes, Hugh L. (Box 156)
- Starnes, Hugh L. (Box 142)
- Starnes, Marian (Box 102)
- Starns, Hugh L. (Box 102)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: family photos included
- Starr, Kenneth (Box 113)
  Biographical information. Alumnus, Law 1973
- Staudenmayer, Nancy A. (Box 102)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Fuqua Business, died 2000
- Stead, Eugene A. (Box 102)
- Stead, Eugene A. (Box 156)
- Stead, Eugene A. (Box 142)
- Stead, William Wallace (Box 102)
- Steckley, Linda G. (Box 102)
- Stedman, Donald J. (Box 102)
- Stedman, Donald J. (Box 142)
- Stedman, Donald John (Box 53)
- Stedman, W. David (Box 113)
  Biographical information. Alumnus; Dist. Alumni Award 1989
- Steege, Deborah Anderson (Box 102)
- Steege, John F. (Box 102)
- Steele, Richard E. (Box 102)
- Steen, Harold K. (Box 102)
- Steen, Harold K. (Box 142)
- Stefansson, Unnstein (Box 102)
- Steinert, Jeff H. (Box 102)
- Steinert, Jeff H. (Box 142)
- Steinhauser, Karen E., 2000 (Box 102)
- Steinmetz, David C. (Box 102)
- Steinmetz, David C. (Box 142)
- Stempfel, Roberts, Jr. (Box 102)
- Stephen, Charles R. (Box 102)
- Stephen, Charles R. (Box 142)
- Stephenson, Harold (Box 102)
- Stephenson, Harold (Box 142)
- Stephenson, Harold (Box 156)
- Stern, Henry R. (Box 102)
- Stern, Henry R. (Box 156)
- Stern, Henry R. (Box 142)
- Stern, Kay Goodman (Box 142)
- Stern, Kay Goodman (Mrs. Sidney J.), Trustee 1988- (Box 118)
- Stern, Mark Andrew (Box 102)
- Stern, William (Box 53)
- Sternbach, Dan (Box 102)
- Sternbach, Dan (Box 142)
- Stevens, Harry R. (Box 102)
- Stevens, Harry R. (Box 142)
- Stevenson, Karl (Box 102)
- Stevenson, Karl (Box 142)
- Stevenson, Lionel (Box 53)
- Stewart, Philip (Box 102)
- Stewart, William James McKelvie (Box 102)
- Stewart, William James McKelvie (Box 142)
- Stewart, William James McKelvie (Box 156)
- Stickel, Delford L. (Box 102)
- Stickel, Delford L. (Box 142)
- Stiles, Gary L. (Box 102)
- Stiles, Kristine (Box 102)
- Still, Bayrd (Box 102)
- Stines, James W. (Box 102)
- Stinespring, William F. (Box 53)
- Stinespring, William F. (Box 142)
- Stocker, Frederick W. (Box 53)
- Stocker, Frederick W. (Box 142)
- Stocker, Frederick W. (Box 156)
- Stockton, Thomas B. (Box 142)
- Stockton, Thomas B., Trustee (Box 118)
- Stoddard, Leland D. (Box 53)
- Stolp, Bryant (Box 102)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Hyperbaric Medicine, 1998
- Stoltenberg, Carl H. (Box 102)
- Stoltenberg, Carl H. (Box 156)
- Stoltenberg, Carl H. (Box 142)
- Stolz, Otto G. (Box 53)
- Stone, Brian (Box 53)
- Stone, Brian (Box 156)
- Stone, Donald Eugene (Box 102)
- Stone, Donald Eugene (Box 142)
- Stone, Edward (Box 53)
- Stone, Martin J. (Box 102)
- Stone, Peter (Box 53)
- Stone, Ronald S. (Box 102)
- Stone, Virginia (Box 102)
- Stone, Virginia (Box 142)
- Stone, Virginia (Box 156)
- Stonier, A.W. (Box 53)
- Stopford, Woodhall (Box 102)
- Storer, Jeff M. (Box 102)
- Storey, Kenneth B. (Box 54)
- Stottlemyer, Paul Clinton (Box 54)
- Stoudemire, George Alan (Box 54)
- Stoughton, W. Vickery (Box 102)
- Stout, Anna (Box 102)
- Stout, Anna (Box 142)
- Strain, Boyd R. (Box 102)
- Strain, Boyd R. (Box 142)
- Strandberg, Victor Hugo (Box 102)
- Strandberg, Victor Hugo (Box 142)
- Strange, John Hadley (Box 102)
- Strassman, Gideon (Box 54)
- Straube, Mark J. (Box 102)
- Straube, Mark J. (Box 142)
- Straumann, Norbert (Box 54)
- Strauss, Claudia (Box 102)
- Strauss, Harold (Box 102)
- Strawson, Peter Frederick (Box 54)
- Strawson, Peter Frederick (Box 142)
- Strawson, Peter Frederick (Box 156)
- Streeter, Arthur H. (Box 54)
- Strelitz, Richard A. (Box 102)
- Strittmatter, Warren J. (Box 102)
- Strobel, Howard A. (Box 103)
- Strobel, Howard A. (Box 156)
- Strobel, Howard A. (Box 142)
- Strohbehn, John Walter (Box 103)
- Strong, Frank R. (Box 54)
- Strong, John W. (Box 103)
- Strong, John W. (Box 142)
- Strowd, Elvin E. (Box 103)
- Strowd, Elvin E. (Box 142)
- Strugnell, John (Box 54)
- Strugnell, John (Box 142)
- Strugnell, John (Box 156)
- Stuart, Charles (Box 54)
- Stubbee, Melinda (Box 103)
- Stubbing, Richard A. (Box 103)
- Stuber, Robert L. (Box 103)
- Stumpf, W.A. (Box 103)
- Stumpf, W.A. (Box 156)
- Stumpf, W.A. (Box 142)
- Stumpf, W.A. (Box 54)
- Sturner, Raymond A. (Box 103)
- Stutz, L. T. (Box 156)
- Styron, William (Box 113)
  Biographical information. Alumnus; Author, 1 of 2
- Styron, William (Box 113)
  Biographical information. Alumnus; Author, 2 of 2
- Suarez, Edward (Box 103)
- Sublett, Henry L., Jr. (Box 54)
- Sugarman, Jeremy (Box 54)
- Sugarman, Jeremy (Box 103)
- Sugden, Herbert Wilfrid (Box 54)
- Suitt, Robert (Box 54)
- Sullenger, Bruce (Box 103)
- Sullivan James B. (Box 103)
- Sullivan, Arthur L. (Box 103)
- Sullivan, Herbert P. (Box 103)
- Sullivan, Herbert P. (Box 156)
- Sullivan, Herbert P. (Box 142)
- Sullivan, John D. (Box 54)
- Sullivan, John D. (Box 103)
- Sullivan, John D. (Box 142)
- Sullivan, John D. (Box 156)
- Sullivan, Martin (Box 103)
- Sullivan, Robert J., Jr. (Box 103)
- Sun, Stella (Box 103)
- Sund, Judy (Box 103)
- Sunderland, Elizabeth R. (Box 103)
- Sunderland, Elizabeth Read (Box 54)
- Sunderland, Elizabeth Read (Box 142)
- Surin, Kenneth J. (Box 103)
- Surwit, Richard Samuel (Box 103)
- Surwit, Richard Samuel (Box 142)
- Sutherland, George Fraser (Box 54)
- Sutherland, George Fraser (Box 142)
- Sutherland, John (Box 103)
- Sutherland, John (Box 142)
- Svetkey, Laura (Box 103)
- Swain, Judith (Box 103)
- Swanson, Jeffrey (Box 103)
- Swanson, Louis E. (Box 54)
- Swanson, Louis E. (Box 103)
- Swanson, Louis E. (Box 142)
- Swanson, Louis E. (Box 156)
- Swartz, Marvin (Box 103)
- Swartzwelder, H. Scott (Box 103)
- Swenson, Deborah (Box 103)
- Swenson, Deborah (Box 142)
- Swett, Francis Huntington (Box 54)
- Swift, David (Box 54)
- Swift, David (Box 142)
- Swift, David (Box 156)
- Swindell, Rebecca (Box 54)
- Sydnor, Charles S. (Box 54)
- Sydnor, Charles S. (Box 103)
- Sydnor, Charles S. (Box 142)
- Sykes, John (Box 103)
- Sykes, Lewis (Box 54)
- Sykes, Lewis (Box 142)
- Sykes, Lewis (Box 156)
- Sylvester, John (Box 103)
- Szasz, Tibor (Box 103)
- Taber, Robert (Box 103)
- Tait, William James, Jr. (Box 54)
- Talbert, Ernest William (Box 54)
- Talbot, Betty Bullock (Box 54)
- Taliaferro, Clay (Box 103)
- Tally, Joe (Box 113)
  Biographical information. Alumnus; Mayor of Fayetteville, N.C. (1949-1953); President, Kiwanis International
- Tan, Teh Y. (Box 103)
- Tanaka, Kimi (Box 156)
- Tanford, Charles (Box 103)
- Tanford, Charles (Box 156)
- Tanford, Charles (Box 142)
- Tangherlini, F. R. (Box 103)
- Tangherlini, F. R. (Box 156)
- Tangherlini, F. R. (Box 142)
- Tannenbaum, Abraham Jack, Trustee (Box 118)
- Tapson, Victor (Box 103)
- Taraba, Wolfgang F. (Box 103)
- Taraba, Wolfgang F. (Box 156)
- Tardiff, Barbara (Box 103)
- Tate, Dorothy (Box 103)
- Tate, Dorothy (Box 142)
- Tate, Dorothy (Box 156)
- Tate, Robert F. (Box 103)
- Tate, Robert H. (Box 156)
- Tate, Robert H. (Box 142)
- Tate, Robert S., Jr. (Box 103)
- Tate, Robert S., Jr. (Box 156)
- Tate, Robert S., Jr. (Box 142)
- Taube, Mortimer (Box 103)
- Taube, Mortimer (Box 142)
- Taube, Mortimer (Box 156)
- Tauchen, George (Box 103)
- Taylor, C. Richard (Box 103)
- Taylor, C. Richard (Box 156)
- Taylor, Donald (Box 103)
- Taylor, Doris (Box 103)
- Taylor, George (Box 54)
- Taylor, George W. (Box 54)
- Taylor, George W. (Box 103)
- Taylor, Grant (Box 54)
- Taylor, Grant (Box 103)
- Taylor, Grant (Box 142)
- Taylor, Haywood Maurice (Box 54)
- Taylor, Hope (Box 103)
- Taylor, Ian (Box 103)
- Taylor, Joe (Box 156)
- Taylor, John H. (Box 103)
- Taylor, John H. (Box 142)
- Taylor, Kerry (Box 103)
- Taylor, Orville W. (Box 54)
- Taylor, Orville W. (Box 103)
- Taylor, Robert E. (Box 103)
- Tedder, Thomas Fletcher (Box 103)
- Teitsworth, Stephen W. (Box 103)
- Telen, Marilyn J. (Box 103)
- Telen, Marilyn J. (Box 142)
- Temple, Arthur (Box 142)
- Temple, Arthur, Trustee (Box 118)
- TePaske, John J. (Box 103)
- TePaske, John J. (Box 142)
- Terborgh, John W. (Box 103)
- Terborgh, John W. (Box 103)
- Terborgh, John W. (Box 142)
- Terry, Robert (Box 103)
- Tetel, Julie A. (Box 103)
- Tetel, Julie A. (Box 142)
- Tetel, Marcel (Box 103)
- Tetel, Marcel (Box 142)
- Thach, William H. (Box 103)
- Thach, William L. (Box 142)
- Thaler, F. Roger (Box 54)
- Thaler, F. Roger (Box 103)
- Thaler, F. Roger (Box 142)
- Thaler, F. Roger (Box 156)
- Thaller, Erich (Box 103)
- Thaller, Erich (Box 142)
- Thaller, Erich (Box 156)
- Tharch, LT. (Box 156)
- Theiss, Ernest S. (Box 103)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: includes wedding portrait of his wife
- Theiss, Ernest S. (Box 142)
- Thewissen, Hans (Box 103)
- Thewissen, Hans (Box 142)
- Thiers, Ralph E. (Box 54)
- Thiers, Ralph E. (Box 103)
- Thiers, Ralph E. (Box 142)
- Thigpen, Richard E. (Box 103)
- Thigpen, Richard E. (Box 156)
- Thigpen, Richard E. (Box 142)
- Thiher, O. Allen, Jr. (Box 103)
- Thomann, Wayne R. (Box 103)
- Thomas, Brinley (Box 103)
- Thomas, Brinley (Box 142)
- Thomas, David (Box 142)
- Thomas, David, Trustee 1988-, Trustee (Box 118)
- Thomas, James Augustus (Box 142)
- Thomas, James Augustus (Box 156)
- Thomas, James Augustus, d. 9/10/1940, Trustee (Box 118)
- Thomas, Jean-Jacques (Box 103)
- Thomas, Jean-Jacques (Box 142)
- Thomas, John E. (Box 103)
- Thomas, John S. (Box 103)
- Thomas, John S. (Box 142)
- Thomas, Joseph Miller (Box 54)
- Thomas, Norman (Box 54)
- Thomas, R. David (Box 113)
  Biographical information. Founder of Wendy's restaurants; Founding donor of the R. David Thomas Center for Executive Education at Fuqua Business
- Thomas, Walter L., Jr. (Box 103)
- Thomas, Walter L., Jr. (Box 156)
- Thomas, Walter Lee, Jr. (Box 54)
- Thompson, Barbara S. (Box 103)
- Thompson, Barbara S. (Box 156)
- Thompson, Edgar T. (Box 54)
- Thompson, Edgar T. (Box 103)
- Thompson, Edgar T. (Box 142)
- Thompson, Edgar T. (Box 156)
- Thompson, Ervin Magnus (Box 103)
- Thompson, Howard K. (Box 54)
- Thompson, Howard K., Jr. (Box 103)
- Thompson, Howard K., Jr. (Box 142)
- Thompson, John Herd (Box 103)
- Thompson, Robert (Box 103)
- Thompson, Robert L. (Box 54)
- Thompson, Robert L. (Box 103)
- Thompson, Robert L. (Box 156)
- Thompson, Robert L. (Box 142)
- Thompson, Robert Warner (Box 103)
- Thompson, Robert Warner (Box 142)
- Thompson, Robert Warner (Box 156)
- Thompson, Thomas T. (Box 54)
- Thompson, William Andrew (Box 54)
- Thompson, William Moreau (Box 54)
- Thomson, Roy (Box 54)
- Thorn, Jennifer (Box 104)
- Thornton, Patricia H. (Box 104)
- Thorpe, Thomas (Box 104)
- Thurstone, Frederick L. (Box 104)
- Thurstone, Frederick L. (Box 142)
- Tiedeman, James S. (Box 104)
- Tifft, Susan (Box 104)
- Tifft, Susan Elizabeth (Box 142)
- Tift, Susan Elizabeth, Trustee (Box 118)
- Tim, Richard (Box 104)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: MDA Clinic, DUMC, 1999
- Timberlake, Susan A., 1996-1999, Trustee (Box 118)
- Timmer, Ashley (Box 104)
- Tindall, George T. (Box 104)
- Tindall, George T. (Box 156)
- Tindall, George T. (Box 142)
- Tindall, John (Box 54)
- Tindall, John (Box 142)
- Ting, Jenny Pan-Yun (Box 104)
- Tirro, Frank P. (Box 54)
- Tirro, Frank P. (Box 142)
- Tiryakian, Edward (Box 104)
- Tiryakian, Edward A. (Box 142)
- Tiryakian, Josefina C. (Box 104)
- Tischendorf, Alfred P. (Box 54)
- Tisdale, Wright (Box 142)
- Tisdale, Wright, d. 9/3/1975, Trustee (Box 118)
- Titus, Bert R. (Box 54)
- Titus, Bert R. (Box 142)
- Tobias, Randall L. (Box 142)
- Tobias, Randall L., Trustee 1988, Trustee (Box 118)
- Todd, (Col.) Raymond P. (Box 142)
- Todd, R. Larry (Box 104)
- Todd, Raymond P. (Box 104)
- Tomlinson, Russell F. (Box 104)
- Tomlinson, Russell F. (Box 156)
- Tomlinson, Russell F. (Box 142)
- Tompkins, Jane (Box 104)
- Tompkins, Jane (Box 142)
- Tompkins, Kevin (Box 104)
- Toms, Clinton White (Box 142)
- Toms, Clinton White, d. 8/29/1936, Trustee (Box 118)
- Toone, Eric John (Box 104)
- Toren, E. Clifford (Box 54)
- Toren, E. Clifford (Box 104)
- Toren, E. Clifford (Box 142)
- Toren, E. Clifford (Box 156)
- Torgovnick, Marianna (Box 104)
- Torgovnick, Marianna (Box 142)
- Tornow, Werner (Box 104)
- Torre, Elias (Box 55)
- Torre, Elias (Box 142)
- Torre, Elias (Box 156)
- Tosteson, Daniel (Box 54)
- Tosteson, Daniel (Box 104)
- Tosteson, Daniel Charles (Box 142)
- Tosteson, Daniel Charles, 1987-1993, Trustee (Box 118)
- Tote, Robert Stuart (Box 104)
- Toth, Alison (Box 104)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Women's Sports Medicine, 2001
- Toth, Cynthia A. (Box 104)
- Tourian, Ara Y. (Box 104)
- Tourian, Ara Y. (Box 142)
- Towe, Kenneth Crawford, Trustee (Box 118)
- Tower, Alan (Box 55)
- Tower, Edward (Box 104)
- Townes, Charles H. (Box 113)
  Biographical information. Alumnus; Nobel Prize for physics (1964); Advisor, Apollo space missions (1960s)
- Trahey, Gregg (Box 104)
- Trangenstein, John A. (Box 104)
- Trask, Tallman (Box 104)
- Travis, Martin B., Jr. (Box 156)
- Travis, Martin B., Jr. (Box 104)
- Travis, Martin B., Jr. (Box 143)
- Treem, William (Box 104)
- Tremi, Vladimir G. (Box 143)
- Tremi, Vladimir G. (Box 104)
- Trent, Josiah C. (Box 55)
- Trent, Josiah C. (Box 156)
- Trevarthen, Robert Richard (Box 104)
- Trevarthen, Robert Richard (Box 143)
- Trickey, Philip H. (Box 104)
- Trickey, Philip H. (Box 143)
- Triebel, Theodore N. (Box 104)
- Trivedi, Kishor (Box 104)
- Trivedi, Kishor (Box 143)
- Trofatter, Kenneth F., Jr. (Box 55)
- Trofatter, Kenneth F., Jr. (Box 143)
- Troth, Dennis C. (Box 55)
- Trotter, Robert L. (Box 55)
- Trotter, Robert L. (Box 143)
- Trought, Williams S. (Box 55)
- Trouillot, Michel-Rolph (Box 55)
- Trowbridge, Lynn M. (Box 104)
- Truesdale, James N. (Box 55)
- Truesdale, James N. (Box 143)
- Trump, Ben (Box 156)
- Trump, Benjamin F. (Box 104)
- Trump, Benjamin F. (Box 143)
- Truskey, George Alexander (Box 104)
- Trustees (Box 115)
- Trustees, General (Box 115)
- Trustees, General, 1979 (Box 115)
- Trustees, General, 1987 (Box 115)
- Trustees, General, 1988 (Box 115)
- Trustees, General, 1989 (Box 115)
- Trustees, General, 1990 (Box 115)
- Trustees, General, 1991 (Box 115)
- Trustees, General, 1998 (Box 115)
- Trustees, General, 2001 (Box 115)
- Trustees, General, 2002 (Box 115)
- Tucci, Debara L. (Box 104)
- Tucker, Gene (Box 157)
- Tucker, Gene M. (Box 55)
- Tucker, Gene M. (Box 104)
- Tucker, Irene (Box 104)
- Tucker, Karen Beth Westerfield (Box 104)
- Tucker, Vance (Box 104)
- Tucker, W. B. (Box 104)
- Tucker, W. B. (Box 143)
- Tufts, Clare Jackson (Box 104)
- Tulis, Jerry (Box 104)
- Tulsky, James A. (Box 104)
- Turk, Herman (Box 104)
- Turk, Herman (Box 143)
- Turk, Herman (Box 157)
- Turlington, Ed (Box 104)
- Turner, Arlin (Box 55)
- Turner, Arlin (Box 143)
- Turner, Arlin (Box 157)
- Turner, Violet Horner (Box 55)
- Turner, Violet Horner (Box 143)
- Turner, Violet Horner (Box 157)
- Turner, Wilfred Dent [NC Lieutenant Gov.], d. 11/8/1933, Trustee (Box 118)
- Turner, William (Box 143)
- Turner, William C. (Box 104)
- Turrentine, Samuel B. (Box 143)
- Turrentine, Samuel B., Trustee (Box 118)
- Turske, Dale W. (Box 104)
- Turske, Dale W. (Box 143)
- Tuthill, Richard Lovejoy (Box 55)
- Tuthill, Richard Lovejoy (Box 143)
- Tuthill, Richard Lovejoy (Box 157)
- Tuthill, Robert C. (Box 55)
- Tuthill, Robert C. (Box 143)
- Tuttle, Lee F. (Box 113)
  Biographical information. Alumnus; Football); Secretary, World Methodist Council
- Twombly, Sharon Renee (Box 104)
- Tyler (Modarressi), Anne (Box 113)
  Biographical information. Alumna; Author; Pulitzer Prize for Breathing Lessons